Christmas in Love is a tv movie, romance, family film directed by Don McBrearty.
Ellie Hartman is an aspiring crafter working in her small
town’s bakery making famous Christmas Kringles.
When the new, big-city CEO Nick Carlingson visits the bakery, he arrives filled
with modernization ideas destined to lay off many employees.
Ellie Hartman, played by Brooke D'Orsay.
Nick Carlingson, played by Daniel Lissing.
Carl North, played by Jamie Spilchuk.
Caroler, played by Chris Renaud.
Grace Hartman, played by Mary-Margaret Humes.
Haley Fagan, played by Carolina Bartczak.
Love Actually is a 2003 Christmas romantic comedy film
written and directed by Richard Curtis.
The film features an ensemble cast, composed predominantly of British
actors, many of whom had worked with Curtis in previous projects.
An international co-production of the United Kingdom, United States
and France, it was mostly filmed on location in London.
The film delves into different aspects of love as shown through 10 separate stories involving a
variety of individuals, many of whom are interlinked as the plot progresses.
The story begins five weeks before Christmas and is played out in a weekly countdown
until the holiday, followed by an epilogue that takes place in the New Year.
The film, Curtis's first as director, was released in the US on 14 November
2003 and a week later in the UK during its theatrical run.
Love Actually was a box-office success, grossing $250.2
million worldwide on a budget of $40–45 million.
The film received mixed reviews and a nomination for the Golden Globe
Award for Best Motion Picture – Musical or Comedy.
In recent years, it has developed a cult following, and is often a staple film shown
during the Christmas period in both the United Kingdom and United States.
A made-for-television short sequel, Red Nose Day Actually, aired in two different versions on
BBC One and NBC in 2017, as part of the fundraising event Red Nose Day 2017.
The film explores themes of holiday, bakery, family holiday, christmas.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.